Cât noroc!
Am găsit spellamiso, o plantă perenă din familia Aoshidare.
Rădăcinile ei, după ce au fost puse la abur și uscate,
pot fi folosite pentru a ameliora febra și durerea.
Oh, vai! Trebuie să deschid magazinul!
Acesta este...
drumul meu.
Povestea mea.
Dacă mi-aș putea pune o dorință,
mi-aș dori să-mi pot decide destinul de una singură.
Episode 1:
Encounter... Changing the Color of Fate
Oglindă, oglinjoară...
Cine-i cea mai frumoasă fată din țară?
Prințule Raj.
Ce este, Sakaki?
Acest bărbat nu este o oglindă.
E un simplu mesager din oraș.
Aha.
Cuvintele lui ar trebui să reflecte ceea ce a văzut, deci ar putea fi considerat una!
Înțeleg. Ei bine, vă rog să vă abțineți de la glume atât de evidente.
Hei, tu!
Nu mai pierde timpul și dă-mi raportul!
A-Am înțeles, Maiestate!
Dacă nu greșesc, sunteți în căutarea celei mai frumoase fete din Tanbarun.
Dacă-mi permiteți, ce părere aveți de acea fată?
„Acea fată”?
Da. E foarte frumoasă,
cu părul ei roșu ca mărul.
Numele ei este Shirayuki, Maiestate.
Îți mulțumesc, domnișoară!
Să nu uitați să vă luați tratamentul!
Voi pleca acum, Shirayuki.
Dle Yoshi, mă voi ruga să fiți sănătos.
Vă mulțumesc pentru așteptare!
Vă voi da acum tratamentul dumneavoastră, dnă Kino.
Nu-ți bate capul cu asta.
Sunt aici doar ca să-ți admir frumusețea.
Vă mulțumesc, dar din moment ce sunteți aici, vă voi pregăti tratamentul.
Am găsit câteva ierburi medicinale bune, deci vă rog să le luați cu dumneavostră.
Ai devenit un botanist desăvârșit.
Mi-aș dori ca bunicii tăi să te poată vedea acum...
Ei bine, d-dna Kino...
Tocmai mi-am amintit! Am lăsat cuptorul pornit!
Poftim?!
Ce neglijență din partea mea.
Bănuiesc că i le pot duce mai târziu.
Ați uitat ceva...
Concubina... prințului Raj?
Da. Cu alte cuvinte, iubita lui.
Asta e absurd.
Sigur nu și-ar dori un om de rând ca mine doar pentru părul meu.
Doar l-aș face de râs.
Prințul Raj te place.
Tomorrow morning, you are to
formally present yourself at the castle.
Take the night to make yourself ready.
This should relieve the pain in Ms. Kino's back
and stop the inflammation of her respiratory tract.
And the father and baby in Ms. Yuri's home
were coming down with a cold.
Okay, all that's left is...
To Ms. Ando
To Ms. Kino
I think that's everything.
Dar nu te învinuiesc deloc.
Adio, Tanbarun.
Scuzați-mă!
Scuzați-mă! E cineva acasă?
Nu pot intra fără permisiune...
Se întunecă...
și începe să mi se facă foame.
Mitsuhide, Kiki! O voi lua înainte!
Hei! Are you really going that way again?
Au...
Ești bine, Zen?
Te-ai lovit la cap? Te doare?
Cât face unu plus unu?
Doi.
Ce? Cine ești?
Sunt eu, Mitsuhide!
Oh, așa te chema?
Kiki! De ce îi faci jocul?!
Și?
Cine ai putea fi tu?
Ce faci atât de adânc în această pădure?
W-Well, see, I was running away...
and I was trying to avoid
running into people on the way...
Părul tău este neobișnuit.
Da, oamenii îmi spun des asta.
Mâna ta... Ești rănit!
What of it?
Sunt un botanist. I have a poultice
that you could apply—
Nu o vreau.
Ce?
Ar putea fi otravă.
You think I'd just say "thanks" and take it?
I'm not some dwarf you
happened to meet in the forest.
My trust is not given so freely.
Hence, I would be a fool to oblige.
Right...
You may as well be on your way then.
Well, what he just said is true.
I guess there are arrogant people everywhere.
Hm? What—
Wh-What are you...?
Not to disappoint you, but I don't
make a habit of carrying poison around.
She got you, Zen.
Sorry about that. The name's Zen.
Eu sunt Shirayuki.
I hope you won't mind treating me, Shirayuki.
Though, it was partly your fault
that I missed my landing.
Ce?
This is an unoccupied house.
We just happen to hang out here.
The one losing at chess
over there is Mitsuhide,
and the one winning handily is Kiki.
Zen, how can you have such confidence
that I'm losing when you aren't even watching?
Just a hunch.
You are losing.
Okay, that should do it.
Uimitor. Ești destul de pricepută la asta, Shirayuki.
Am ceva experiență.
Ți-am spus că sunt un botanist, nu?
Da. Așa este.
Deci de ce a fugit de acasă un botanist ca tine?
Asta nu e important.
Voi merge la o plimbare.
Deci de ce ai venit cu mine?
I wouldn't be a gentleman if I let an
injured girl walk in the woods by herself.
Okay then.
I became used to the mountains and forests
while studying to become an herbalist.
It's refreshing how the time and air
seem to move differently here than in town.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
You really meant that just now, didn't you?
Ow!
Ow...
Oh, it's caught.
There are a few strands longer than the others.
Huh?
Oh, I must've missed it.
Sorry, Zen. Will you cut it for me?
Huh?
It doesn't have to be straight.
No can do. I couldn't possibly cut a lady's hair!
What?
Does cutting your long hair have something
to do with why you ran away from home?
If you tell me the reason, I can help you.
Really now.
Hm?
You were told to become his concubine?!
By a famous rich boy who grew up surrounded
by escorts and a silver spoon in his mouth.
He thought my red hair was unusual,
and so he wanted to make me his own.
I might as well have been nothing more
than an apple he bought if I had done as he'd said.
Shirayu—
That's why I thought I'd have
him tire of it strand by strand
and left my hair behind.
You made the right call!
Huh?
Good job getting away from that lowlife.
That red of yours is important to you.
My... red?
Yeah.
Red is supposed to be the color of fate, right?
It might cause you nothing
but trouble right now,
but that's because it's
connected to something good.
I-I won't deny that I admire
your way of thinking...
Oh? Is that respect?
She doesn't seem like a
suspicious person after all, huh?
Not only that,
but Zen seems to really like her.
What's this?
That's the ribbon I tied my hair in!
Ce?
My dearest Shirayuki,
When the shining sun sets into the horizon
I shall appear before thine eyes
I will await you at the border
My request is that you begin to make your way there
An acquaintance from your homeland
My dearest Shirayuki,
When the shining sun sets into the horizon
I shall appear before thine eyes
I will await you at the border
My request is that you begin to make your way there
An acquaintance from your homeland
When the shining sun sets into the horizon
I shall appear before thine eyes
I will await you at the border
My request is that you begin to make your way there
My dearest Shirayuki,
When the shining sun sets into the horizon
I shall appear before thine eyes
I will await you at the border
My request is that you begin to make your way there
An acquaintance from your homeland
When the shining sun sets into the horizon
I shall appear before thine eyes
I will await you at the border
My request is that you begin to make your way there
My dearest Shirayuki,
When the shining sun sets into the horizon
I shall appear before thine eyes
I will await you at the border
My request is that you begin to make your way there
An acquaintance from your homeland
My dearest Shirayuki,
When the shining sun sets into the horizon
I shall appear before thine eyes
I will await you at the border
My request is that you begin to make your way there
An acquaintance from your homeland
When the shining sun sets into the horizon
I shall appear before thine eyes
I will await you at the border
My request is that you begin to make your way there
An acquaintance from your homeland
When the shining sun sets into the horizon
I shall appear before thine eyes
I will await you at the border
My request is that you begin to make your way there
An acquaintance from your homeland
Deci ești din Tanbarun, nu?
The sender came all the way to
the border to give you this, you know.
He seems to be a rather spiteful gentleman.
Right?
This is no laughing matter!
Was it so serious that you
had to flee across the border?
Because it's him...
He's the first prince of Tanbarun...
Raj—
was the name...
of that idiot prince, wasn't it?
Are you all right?
So he's such a moron that rumors
have even spread to neighboring countries...
It's because it's him, huh?
He probably ordered for a full search,
including a check of the border crossing records.
He would go that far, huh?
He's probably the type that considers something
his own the moment he sets his eyes on it.
Even if it means taking away my freedom...
No way, right?
Hm?
It's starting to go bad.
I guess no one would want this red anymore.
Just kidding...
Zen?
Zen...
You're so impolite.
Don't do that, Zen. You have hands.
What're you—
Pick to either talk or eat.
Who asked you? Stay out of it!
Man, that hurts.
Zen!
What?!
I said something stupid. Sorry.
Shirayuki, don't eat that apple.
Ce?
Kiki, Mitsuhide...
Nu vă supărați...
Zen!
Ce este, Zen?
E otrăvit!
Ai un antidot?!
Dă-mi o secundă!
It's no use.
I can't prepare one with just these.
Dacă nu mă grăbesc...
Oh? Miss Shirayuki was not
the one who ate the apple?
Cine ești?!
You're...
Hm... Well, no matter.
What's going on?!
Worry not. I know someone
who has your antidote.
I trust that you will come with me quietly?
Oh, so it's you?
I see. I'm surprised.
So the red hair you left behind
was real after all.
Excuse me.
What about the antidote for my friend?
Don't be so hasty.
You see, Miss Shirayuki...
The world is a frightening place.
When you fled following
my attempts to court you,
I became the laughingstock of every town,
not to mention the royal palace.
Thanks to you, the public's
opinion of me has plummeted.
However, everyone's saying
it's also your fault, so it must be true.
Thus, in order to clear my good name,
I'll have you ask to be my concubine.
What?!
Even if you are just a lowly town girl,
I did not want to cause a woman embarrassment,
and so this is the solution I reached
after much deliberation.
D-Did I hear him right?
Um, more importantly,
what about the antidote?
Do you think I could get the antidote
for my friend, Prince Raj?
Oh, right. Answer me with a nod
and I will have it promptly delivered.
Or would you rather
visit him with one of these?
Red is supposed to be the color of fate, right?
It might cause you nothing
but trouble right now,
but that's because it's
connected to something good.
He... He gave those words to me...
Hm...
As far as I am concerned,
now that I know how easy on the eyes you are,
I do not wish for you to be far from me.
H-How dare...
Oh, my apologies.
Prince Raj. Do as you wish
and take me.
Wait, stay back!
Huh?
I object!
Zen!
Bastard!
I refuse to let you sully that girl's ears
with any more of your dirty jokes.
Zen!
Hey, Shirayuki. Tie this for me.
Wait. Before that, how are you feeling?
I've been slowly building up an immunity
to poison for a situation like this.
Dar...
Înțeleg!
So you are the one who was poisoned!
Oh, that was unfortunate.
I was planning on immobilizing Miss Shirayuki
and taking her home with me.
So you're the one to blame for those apples.
Watch your tongue, boy!
My social status is far beyond yours.
Excuse me, first prince of Tanbarun,
Prince Raj Schenazade.
Huh?
I didn't want to do this,
but let me introduce myself.
Hm? Isn't that crest...
I don't believe we've met before.
Eu sunt al doilea prinț al Regatului Clarines, Zen Wistalia!
Al doilea...
Un p-prinț?!
Z-Zen, get a hold of yourself!
Do you know who I am?
Cât face unu plus unu?!
I'm serious, Shirayuki.
But I never imagined that a prince from
a neighboring kingdom would poison me.
Prințule Raj.
E-Eu?!
But... you have no proof that
I was the one who poisoned you!
There's plenty, isn't there?
You're more than welcome to testify in court.
Th-That's...
Shall we make a trade,
you dunce of a prince?
If you don't want your foolish
actions to be made public,
then swear you will never approach
Shirayuki again or even utter her name.
How is Miss Shirayuki—
A-All right! I swear!
On my life!
Shirayuki, I'm sure you have
quite a few things to say to him.
Huh?
Now's your chance to
tell him how you really feel.
Let it all out.
Okay.
Prințule Raj.
I hope you feel better with this.
From what I can see, you're coming
down with a severe case of shock.
Also...
Hurry up and give the antidote to Zen.
Okay...
Thank you.
Ce este, Shirayuki?
Îți mulțumesc că m-ai ajutat.
Dar îmi pare rău.
Am devenit otrava ta.
Încerci cumva să faci o glumă?
Is it because you share the same red
as the poisoned apple I bit into?
Not really...
It's all right. Nothing you need
to apologize for, Shirayuki.
Zen ate it of his own accord.
The three of us should
have been more careful.
That's all.
Mitsuhide got all teary-eyed and went about
declaring that he'd go down with Zen.
Don't talk about that!
How sad.
Okay, okay.
The next time I get some fruit,
I'll have Mitsuhide peel it first.
Was that the point?!
Shirayuki, do you remember
what I said in the forest?
I'd like to believe we were
brought here together by fate.
In this very forest,
where we found you traveling,
we met and tried to protect each other.
Whether that becomes the poison
that ends our encounter here...
or something that ties us together
is for you to decide.
Is that really something I can decide?
Of course! I've been choosing my own fate too.
The only one who should decide
which path to follow is yourself.
Zen...
What?
The way you think really is amazing.
It's not how I think, though, it's how I live.
What's your answer?
This is the story I will call my own.
If I could make a wish,
on this path that lies before us,
the sound of the turning pages in this story
will echo like the sound
of our overlapping footsteps.
Eu...
Mă bucur să te văd din nou, Shirayuki.
Clarines is a really nice place.
Were you waiting for me?
Ce? Shirayuki nu e aici?
...motivul pentru care m-am decis să vin în această țară.
Did you give up on escaping, Red?
Episode 2:
Following the Sound of Your Heart